

# SUMANT GAWADE

**B.Tech. - Information Technology** Ph: +91-9923990784

Email: yashgawade282002@gmail.com Pune, Maharashtra, India - 410507



LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sumantgawade

### **BRIEF SUMMARY**

Seeking a beginner role to enhance and explore my technical knowledge gained at D Y Patil University in the last four years. I hold Internship Skills in AWS and Java, and won the Digital Poster Making held at the campus. I consider myself a responsible and disciplined person.

### **KEY EXPERTISE**

AWS **DBMS** Dotnet cybersecurity PowerBI Java

### **EDUCATION**

School of Engineering and Technology  B.Tech Information Technology   CGPA: 8.51 / 10	2020 - 2024
Tatya Saheb Musale Vidhyalaya and Junior College  12 <sup>th</sup>   MSBSHSE   Percentage: 70 / 100	2020
Milagris High School  10 <sup>th</sup>   MSBSHSE   Percentage: 78 / 100	2018

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Intern Crowd LLP   IT / Computers - Software Internship	22 Mar, 2023 - 23 Apr, 2023
BrainOvision Solutions PVT LTD   IT / Computers - Software Internship	18 Jul, 2022 - 09 Aug, 2022

# **INTERNSHIPS**

Intern Crowd Java Developer	22 Mar, 2023 - 22 Apr, 2023
BrainOvision Solutions PVT.LTD Cloud Engineer	18 Jul, 2022 - 08 Aug, 2022

#### **PROJECTS**

### Final Year Project- Handwritten Language Detection Using Deep Learning

Using this model we can copy various types of handwritten languages and copied text is saved in the computer language which is easy for readable.

### Third Year Project- Online Complaint Registration And Management System

This project is to help the public in knowing their place details and getting their problems solved in online without going to the officer regularly until the problem is solved.

### **PUBLICATIONS / RESEARCH / WHITE PAPERS**

#### Handwritten Language Detection Using Deep Learning

24 Feb, 2024

Research Paper | Hinweis Second International Conference on Advanced Research in Engineering and Technology No. of Authors: 4

Handwritten language detection research focuses on the development and evaluation of machine learning models for the automated identification of the language in handwritten texts.

A Systematic Literature Review Method on Cryptography for Data Sharing Encryption on Cloud Computing

Research Paper

# ASSESSMENTS / CERTIFICATIONS

**Cyber Vidyapeeth Foundation** 

Key Skills: Cybersecurity

**Foundations of Cybersecurity Course** 

Key Skills: Cybersecurity

# **SEMINARS / TRAININGS / WORKSHOPS**

Power BI Training Institute Name: Infosys Springboard

01 Mar, 2024 - 08 Mar, 2024

04 Dec, 2023 - 09 Dec, 2023

Key Skills: Power BI

36 hours Company Specific Aptitude & Soft Skills Training

Institute Name: D Y Patil School of Engineering, Ambi, Pune

Key Skills: Apptitude SoftSkills

# **WEB LINKS**

o Github - https://github.com/sumantgawade

Email: yashgawade282002@gmail.com

# PERSONAL DETAILS

Gender: Male Date of Birth: 28 Aug, 2002

Marital Status: Single Known Languages: English Marathi Hindi

Current Address: D Y Patil Ambi Talegaon, Pune, Maharashtra, Phone Number: +91-9923990784

India - 410507